Frank Ormsby papers, circa 1967-2004
Emory University
- Printed material, circa 1965-1991, Series 5; Box 30: folders 9-72 - Box 34; OP 6, 10-19
  - Other printed material, Subseries 5.3; Box 32: folders 20-74 - Box 34: folders 1-6; OP 11, 13-19
    - The Lyric Players Theatre, Belfast (1969-1980, 1996) [includes: John Keane's The Field, Sean O'Casey's The Shadow of a Gunman, Tom Stoppard's Rosencrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead, Sean O'Casey's The Silver Tassie, John Boyd's The Flats (Belfast 1971), Samuel Beckett's Waiting for Godot, Edna O'Brien's The Gathering, Peter Shaffer's Equus, W. B. Yeats's The Cuchulain Cycle, John Boyd's Facing North, William Shakespeare's The Merchant of Venice] (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Queen's Film Theatre (1969-1970) (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Assorted Theaters [includes: Abbey Theatre, Grove Theatre, Irish Theatre Company, Royal Shakespeare Company, Ulster Theatre Company] (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Programs for Miscellaneous Events
    - Promotional poster, Festival 1969, The Honest Ulsterman, November Pamphlet [Heaney, Foley, Simmons, Richards] (Box OP13)
    - Belfast Group announcements 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Queens University Belfast English Society events 1976-1996 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Fringe Festival, Queens University Belfast, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Lindy Guinness: An Exhibition of Paintings, Watercolours and Drawings, 1969-1976 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - W. B. Yeats International Summer School, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Colin Middleton: Paintings 1976-1977, exhibit 1977 [program] (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Fringe Festival, Queens University Belfast, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Noel Connor: Drawing from Poetry, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Arthur Campbell: Watercolours and Photographs Since 1935, exhibit 1984 [program] (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Ross Wilson, art exhibit, 1993 [program] (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Field Day Theatre Company announcements [undated] (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Promotional poster, Queens University Belfast opening for Modern Irish Poetry, ed. by Patrick Crotty (1995) [Carson, McGuckian, Mooney, O' Searcaigh, McCarthy] (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Promotional poster, Queens University Belfast (1995) [Heaney, Longley, Hammond] (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous invitations (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous literary programs (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous film programs (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous art programs (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Catalogues and Stocklists
    - Anvil Press Poetry (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Blackstaff Press (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Dolmen Press Books (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Gallery Press, mailings [stocklists] (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Material
    - The James Joyce Museum, Dun Laoghaire [program] (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - The Tyrone Guthrie Centre at Annaghmakerrig (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous printed material [includes: Tribes, documentary film promotional poster] (Box OP19)
- Photographs, Series 6; Box 34: folders 7-30
  The Frank Ormsby collection holds an assortment of photographs not only of Ormsby himself but of many of the major Irish and British writers of the late twentieth-century. Many of the photographs are head shots of high quality and were originally intended for promotional use by either the writer or the publishing house representing the writer. There are two subsections of photographs. One contains photos of Ormsby, and many of these are snapshots from readings or other literary events. The other subsection contains photographs of other literary figures. Folders dedicated to photographs of individual writers are arranged alphabetically by author. A photograph of a particular group of writers is organized separately.
  - Frank Ormsby
  - Ormsby at Canadian Association for Irish Studies, University of Saskatchewan, February 1987 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Ormsby on trip to Romania sponsored by The British Council, 2-10 October 1987 [with Fleur Adcock] (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Ormsby in Tallinn, Estonia, 28 October - 4 November 1995 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Ormsby negatives (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Others
  - Ewart, Gavin [1] (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Fanthorpe, U. A. [1] (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Fiacc, Padraic[1] (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Forbes, Duncan [1] (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Heaney, Seamus [2] (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Johnston, Jennifer [2] (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Longley, Michael [1] (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - MacLaverty, Bernard [1] (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - MacNeice, Louis [1] (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Paulin, Tom [1] (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Prorok, Leszek [1] (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Raine, Craig [1] (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Reid, Christopher [1] (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Rumens, Carol [2] (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Scott, David [1] (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Seidel, Fred [1] (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Simmons, James [1] (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Waterman, Andrew [1] (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Anonymous (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Groups
  - Williams, Patrick; Campbell, Kerry; Gorman, Damian (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Personal materials, Series 7; Box 34: folders 31-33
  This small series contains various unclassifiable or disparate items. Some are of a personal nature.
  - Miscellaneous royalty calculations (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Enniskillen Integrated Primary School materials (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous personal materials (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Unprocessed additions, Series 8; Boxes 35-40
  This series consists of unprocessed additions received in 2009, and includes writings by Ormsby, writings by others including Michael Longley and James Simmons, correspondence, and printed material. The writings include some of Ormsby's first attempts at poetry, dating from 1958-1959, in addition his poetry notebooks from 1994-2004.
  - Unprocessed additions (Box 35-40)